# Slava Trofimov

## **Full Stack Developer**

Richmond Hill, ON L4C 1E5 slava@trofimov.ca +1 289 980 8683

I'm a Full Stack Developer from Toronto.

I have more than 12 years of experience as a Front End Developer and 3+ years as a Full Stack Developer.

Experienced in several high-traffic projects from educational to real-time data management and social networks.

I specialize in all aspects of web development from basic HTML/CSS/JS coding to creating full-scale web applications with rich REST API(PHP/NodeJs).

My primary stack is Laravel+Vue but I have experience with WordPress, Opencart, Electron, React, NodeJs, Python, etc. Have good DevOps skills, and experience with all common databases such as MySQL, MongoDB, SQLite, etc. Using Git / GitLab / BitBucket, Jira, Slack, Linux/Mac/Windows daily.

A fast learner, problem solver, and team player, always seeking skill improvement and better practices.

# Work Experience

#### **Senior Front End Developer**

Codepxl - Toronto, ON January 2019 to Present

Toronto-based App development, website design, complex system development, and graphic design agency. HTML5, SAAS, Vue3/Nuxt3, SPA, Laravel, WordPress, OpenCart projects development.

#### **Front End Developer**

EvolutionInDesignZ - Toronto, ON May 2018 to December 2018

Web app development, website development, graphic design and online marketing agency. HTML5,SCSS, SPA, VueJS, Laravel, OpenCart, Wordpress projects development.

#### **Web Master**

Electrolight Enterprises - Toronto, ON August 2017 to May 2018

Lighting & Design Services for the GTA. Web mastering, content management.

#### Front End Developer

iMoan.ru - Moscow August 2015 to July 2017 One of the fast-growing e-commerce projects in the adult industry. HTML5 (pug) / CSS3 (Less) / JS(jQuery, Angular) / PHP (Opencart) coding, Web/UI design, VPS administrative, SEO, Projectmenagment, work with remote employees.

## **Lead Front End Developer**

Web Solution Ltd. - Moscow March 2013 to August 2015

Web design studio with hundreds of clients. Front-end development and UI design. HTML5 (pug) /CSS3 (Less) / JS (jQuery) / PHP (Joomla, WordPress, Opencart) coding.

## **Front End Developer**

Giftery corp. - Moscow February 2012 to March 2013

Startup Giftery.ru is buyers bonus card system with many of commerce partners. Front-end development. HTML5 / CSS3 (Less) / JS (jQuery) / PHP (1C bitrix) coding.

## Front End Developer

Predestination.ru - Moscow January 2011 to February 2012

Popular business training project with multiple courses and programs. Front-end development, Web design, UI Design. HTML / CSS / JS (jQuery) / PHP (WordPress) coding.

## Junior Front End Developer

KM ONLINE, R-STYLE COMPANY GROUP - Moscow 2008 to 2010

News, entertainment and media company. Work on social media project - vkrugudruzei.ru. Front-end development. HTML / CSS / JS (jQuery) coding.

#### Education

#### **Master in Computer Science**

Moscow State Open University - Moscow 2007 to 2008

# **Diploma in Computer Science**

Moscow Technological University - Moscow 2003 to 2007

# Skills

- Javascript (7 years)
- HTML5 (10+ years)
- CSS (10+ years)
- Vue.js (4 years)
- Angular (1 year)
- Php (3 years)

- Python (1 year)
- Bootstrap (4 years)
- SPA (2 years)
- Laravel (2 years)
- Adobe Photoshop (5 years)
- Wordpress (5 years)
- Opencart (5 years)
- Django (2 years)
- Node.js
- GitHub (5 years)
- AJAX (7 years)
- UI / UX (7 years)
- RESTful API (6 years)
- SCSS (6 years)
- Responsive Styling (10+ years)
- Laravel (3 years)
- ElectronJS (2 years)
- MySQL (5 years)
- MongoDB (1 year)
- NuxtJS (1 year)
- Tailwind CSS (1 year)
- Docker (3 years)

# Languages

- English Fluent
- Russian Expert

## Links

https://github.com/pmbstyle

https://trofimov.ca

https://www.linkedin.com/in/slava-trofimov-ca